Kheel, Theodore W. Newspaper Clipping File 6017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- United Nations Rio Conference; Earth Pledge; Earth Summit; Earth Summit Times, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- United Nations Conferences - Vienna and Cairo -Sustainable Development, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Vietnam War - Paris Peace Talks (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Wage Stabilization - Korean War (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Wage Stabilization - Nixon Program, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Wage Stabilization - World War II (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Robert F. Wagner (on leaving office as Mayor) (Box 3, Folder 79)
- War Labor Board, 1942-1946 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- West Side Convention Center (Box 3, Folder 81)
- West Side Highway (Westway) (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Western Union - Ouster of Chairman and CEO Flanagan (Box 3, Folder 83)
- World Trade Center (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Whitney M. Young, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 85)
- News Clippings, 1941-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- News Clippings, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- News Clippings, 1970-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Unused Duplicated, 1945-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- News Clippings, 1977-1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- News Clippings - Foundation on Employee Health Medical Care and Welfare, Inc. - American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- News Clippings - Master Index, 1941-1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Theodore W. Kheel Scrapbook (1997-1999) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  binder of news clippings
- Theodore W. Kheel Scrapbook (2000-2002) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  binder full of clippings